{
    "subject": "resource/Vladimir_Dvornikovi\u0107",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1956",
    "human_readable": "Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 died in 1956.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9669281244277954,
            "question": "If Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 died in 1956, how old could he have been?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9053212404251099,
            "question": "When did Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310107588768005,
            "question": "Was Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 alive in the year 1957?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635368704795837,
            "question": "What year is associated with Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021217346191406,
            "question": "What historical events might have happened around the year of Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6045166254043579,
            "question": "What could have been some of the major advancements or discoveries happening around the time of Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5547127723693848,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 besides his year of death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4164450168609619,
            "question": "In what century did Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3818405568599701,
            "question": "Could Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 have been born before the year 1900?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33306431770324707,
            "question": "Can you think of any significant people who may have lived during the same period as Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 died in 1956.",
            "html": "dbpedia_594_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 have been born before the year 1900?",
            "html": "dbpedia_594_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what century did Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_594_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything else about Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 besides his year of death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_594_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_594_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_594/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt` mentions Vladimir Dvornikovi\u0107 and states that he \"He died in 1956 in Belgrade.\"\n\nGiven this information, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the document, which states \"He died in 1956 in Belgrade.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}